# Karim Abdelhalim

## Web & mobile application developer

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a passionate self-taught front-end developer. I love coding creative UIs and bringing designs to life with clean, efficient code. My expertise includes building responsive and user-friendly websites and applications, constantly learning and adapting to new technologies and trends to deliver the best digital experiences.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Front-end Developer at MedC

OCT 2023 - 2024

Collaborated with a skilled team to deliver a medical educational app, focusing on enhancing the user interface and experience.

- Development of Mobile application UI
- Enhancements on the admin dashboard website

## Full-stack Developer at Ringfill

DEC 2023 - 2024

Contributed to both frontend and backend development for various tasks such as:

- Development of Mobile application & Website UI
- Update APIs

#### **COURSEES & TRAININGS**

#### **DEPI** | React Development

April 2024 - OCT2024

## Ministry of communications Information, Egypt

- Cloud computing | web development (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript)
- Front-end development (React.js, Tailwind CSS)
- Back-end development (node.js, Express.js, MongoDB)
- Soft Skills

#### Front-end Development

2023

## **Almenor Platform**

- Web development using HTML5 & CSS3
- Mastering CSS flex, CSS Grid & CSS Animation
- JavaScript for expert levels
- Git & GitHub

## **PROJECTS**

#### Babel library

- Description: A library app that offers a diverse collection of books, each with comprehensive information. It includes features such as a search bar, the ability to add books to your favorites, a reading progress tracker, and a dedicated screen for adding your favorite quotes.
- Technologies: Next.js, tailwind CSS, Shadon UI, React Native (expo), firebase, Figma
- Links: GitHub

## UnityCare hospital

- Description: This platform was developed to provide a comprehensive solution for healthcare services. It allows patients to easily book appointments, access information about doctors and specialties, and stay informed with the latest medical news. The website is designed to be scalable, secure, and user-friendly.
- Technologies: Next.js, TypeScript, tailwind CSS, Shadcn UI, node.js, MongoDB
- Links: GitHub Web Page

### **CONTACTS**

**Phone**: (+20) 102 309 6263 **Address**: Egypt, Cairo

Email: Karimoda66@gmail.com

#### LINKS

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/karim-abdel-

halim-95a97a248/Karim248119

**GitHub**: <a href="https://github.com/Karim248119">https://github.com/Karim248119</a> **Portfolio**: <a href="https://karim-a-hassan.vercel.app">https://karim-a-hassan.vercel.app</a>

#### **EDUCATION**

ASU Mechanical engineering (Mechatronic department)

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## **Programing Languages**

- HTML Type Script
- CSS Python
- Java Scripts

#### Front-end

- React.js Next.js
- Shadcn UI
- React Native

C++

#### Back-end

Node.js
Express.js

## **Version Control**

• Git • GitHub

## Design/Prototyping

• Figma

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **Arabic (Native)**

**English**